QuizApp.Data.config = {"name": "Quiz App"};
QuizApp.Data.questions = [
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using Ember.js?",
	"difficultyLevel": "low",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"}
				],
    "answer": 0,
    "pageId":1,
    "questionId":1
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using jQuery Mobile?",
	"difficultyLevel": "medium",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"} 
				],
    "answer": 1,
    "pageId":1,
  	"questionId":2
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using Java EE?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"} 
				],
    "answer": 2,
    "pageId":1,
	"questionId":3
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using ASP.NET?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"} 
				],
    "answer": 0,
    "pageId": 2,
    "questionId":4
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using RoR?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"},
				 {"option": "God knows"}
				],
    "answer": 1,
    "pageId": 2,
    "questionId":5
  },
{
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using Ember.js?",
	"difficultyLevel": "low",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"}
				],
    "answer": 0,
    "pageId":2,
    "questionId":6
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using jQuery Mobile?",
	"difficultyLevel": "medium",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"} 
				],
    "answer": 1,
    "pageId":3,
  	"questionId":7
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using Java EE?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"} 
				],
    "answer": 2,
    "pageId":3,
	"questionId":8
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using ASP.NET?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"} 
				],
    "answer": 0,
    "pageId": 3,
    "questionId":9
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you develop a quiz app using RoR?",
	"difficultyLevel": "high",
    "options": [ {"option": "Yes"},
				 {"option": "No"},
				 {"option": "Not sure"},
				 {"option": "God knows"}
				],
    "answer": 1,
    "pageId": 4,
    "questionId":10
  }
];


